Savings Bank of Manchester Records
© 2004 University of Connecticut
Series III: Advertising and Public Relations Records ( 1968-2004 ) is extensive, including seven large advertising scrapbooks with SBM ads and bank-related articles (1968-1983). There is a gap in this portion of the collection from 1984-1993. Photocopies of a large number of SBM newspaper ads, as well as some sponsorship ads in programs, playbills, and other similar publications, are filed in the collection for 1994-2003. It should also be noted that the few pre-1968 advertisements found in the collection have been filed under "historical" in this series. Another large part of the Advertising/P.R. series are the "promotional" collections, including files with materials from specific promotions or ad campaigns, files with marketing materials from branch openings, many SBM-logo promotional give-away items, and other ephemeral promotional items and records. Public Relations files include several large folders of donation records (including requests for funds, copies of disbursed checks, or denials for requests), as well as correspondence, a few SBM historical items including an SBM history (1976), a few press releases, and plaques of recognition. Finally, the Advertising/P.R. series contains many oversized SBM lobby signs, banners, and a few large framed SBM photographs from bank offices.
Series IV: Multimedia materials ( ca.1980-2004, bulk 1990-2004 ) contains audio, video, beta, C.D., and other tapes containing mostly audio and video of commercial footage.
Series V: Photographs ( 1960s-2000s ) is comprised of black-and-white employee portraits, "photo-opportunity" type pictures, albums with SBM event photographs, and several older photographs of the bank's various branch offices and employees.
Related Material
Archives & Special Collections has a substantial collection of materials pertaining to Connecticut businesses. For detailed information on these collections please contact the curator or ask at the reference desk.
Separated Material
The following materials have been separated from the collection and cataloged:
Richard Urban. Connecticut: Chartered for Progress. Dodd Call No. D1688 (2 copies)
Weldon Welfling. Mutaul Savings Banks; the evolution of a financial intermediary. Dodd Call No. A5093
Sandler O'Neill & Partners, L.P. Prospectus: Connecticut Bancshares, Inc. Dodd Call No.
Sandler O'Neill & Partners, L.P. Prospectus Sumplement. Dodd Call No.
Financial Women International. 1995 Professional Network--Membership Directory. Dodd Call No.
Savings Bank of Manchester. "Pulling Together". Dodd Call No.
Savings Bank of Manchester. "Between Friends". Dodd Call No.
Savings Bank of Manchester. "Savings Bank Country News". Dodd Call No.
Savings Bank of Manchester. "The News". Dodd Call No.
Savings Bank of Manchester. "Savings Bank of Manchester Newsletter". Dodd Call No.
Index Terms
This record series is indexed under the following controlled access subject terms.
Persons:
Cheney, Frank, Jr.
Places:
Manchester, Conn.
Subjects:
Savings Bank of Manchester--History.; Banks and banking--Connecticut.; Connecticut--Businesses, industries and trades--Banking.; Manchester (Conn.)--Businesses, industries and trades--Banking.
Document Types:
Correspondence.; Publications.; Photographs.; Administrative Records.; Financial Records.; Minutes.; Press releases.; Videocassettes.; Audio cassettes.; Audio visual materials.; Fliers. [printed matter]; Photocopies.; Notes.; Books.; Scrap-Books.; Stuffed toys.; Posters.; Newsletters.; Histories.
Occupations:
Banking.
Restrictions on Access
There are no access restrictions on this collection.
Acquisition Information
The collection was donated to Archives & Special Collections in 2004.
Detailed Description
- Series I: Administrative Records, undated, 1905-2003
  - Reference Guide and Purchasing Manual, ca. 2000 (Box 58:, Folder 528)
  - Subseries A: Annual Meeting Records, 1969-1970, 1977-1995
    - 1969 (Box 1:, Folder 1)
    - 1970 (Box 1:, Folder 2)
    - 1977 (Box 1:, Folder 3)
    - 1978 (Box 1:, Folder 4)
    - 1979 (Box 1:, Folder 5)
    - 1980 (Box 1:, Folder 6)
    - 1981 (Box 1:, Folder 7)
    - 1982 (Box 1:, Folder 8)
    - 1983 (Box 1:, Folder 9)
    - 1984 (Box 1:, Folder 10-11)
    - 1985 (Box 1:, Folder 12)
    - 1986 (Box 1:, Folder 13-14)
    - 1987 (Box 1:, Folder 15-16)
    - 1988 (Box 1:, Folder 17-18)
    - 1989 (Box 1:, Folder 19-20)
    - 1990 (Box 1:, Folder 21-22)
    - 1991 (Box 1:, Folder 23)
    - 1992 (Box 1:, Folder 24-25)
    - 1993 (Box 2:, Folder 26)
    - 1994 (Box 2:, Folder 27-28)
    - 1995 (Box 2:, Folder 29-30)
  - Subseries B: Board of Directors Records, 1905-1997; [Note: Until 1982 the Board of Directors and Executive Committee materials were maintained separately. After 1982, these records were merged. This practice is reflected in the arrangment of this series.]
    - Board of Directors Ledger - Home Bank & Trust Company (before SBM merger), 1920-1927 (Box 3)
    - Board of Directors Ledger - SBM, 1905-1930 (Box 4)
    - Board of Directors Ledger- Loose Items, 1905-1930 (Box 2:, Folder 31)
    - Board of Directors Ledgers- Loose Items, 1930-1941 (Box 2:, Folder 32)
    - Board of Directors Record Book, 1930-1941 (Box 5)
    - Board of Directors Record Book, 1941-1953 (Box 6)
    - Board of Directors Record Book, 1954-1958 (Box 7)
    - Board of Directors Resolution Certificate - President Frank Cheney Retirement, 1954 (Box 59)
    - Board of Directors Record Book, 1959-1961 (Box 8)
    - Board of Directors Record Book, 1961-1963 (Box 9)
    - Board of Directors Record Book, 1963-1965 (Box 10)
    - Board of Directors Record Book, 1966-1968 (Box 11)
    - Board of Directors Record Book, 1969-1971 (Box 12)
    - Board of Directors Record Book, 1972-1974 (Box 13)
    - Board of Directors Record Book, 1975-1976 (Box 14)
    - Board of Directors Record Book, 1977-1978 (Box 15)
    - Board of Directors Record Book, 1978-1979 (Box 16)
    - Board of Directors Record Book, 1980-1982 (Box 17)
    - Board of Directors Records, 1982 Jun-Dec (Box 18:, Folder 33)
    - Executive Committee Records, 1982 (Box 18:, Folder 34-35)
    - Board of Directors Records, 1983 (Box 18:, Folder 36)
    - Executive Committee Records, 1983 (Box 18:, Folder 37-38)
    - Board of Directors Records, 1984 (Box 18:, Folder 39)
    - Executive Committee Records, 1984 (Box 18:, Folder 40-41)
    - Board of Directors Records, 1985 (Box 18:, Folder 42)
    - Executive Committee Records, 1985 (Box 18:, Folder 43-44)
    - Board of Directors Records, 1986 (Box 18:, Folder 45)
    - Executive Committee Records, 1986 (Box 18:, Folder 46-47)
    - Board of Directors Records, 1987 (Box 18:, Folder 48)
    - Executive Committee Records, 1987 (Box 18:, Folder 49-50)
    - Board of Directors Records, 1988 (Box 18:, Folder 51)
    - Executive Committee Records, 1988 (Box 18:, Folder 52-53)
    - Board of Directors, 1989 (Box 18:, Folder 54)
    - Executive Committee Records, 1989 (Box 18:, Folder 55-56)
    - Board of Directors Records, 1990 (Box 19:, Folder 57-58)
    - Executive Committee Records, 1990 (Box 19:, Folder 59-60)
    - Board of Directors Records, 1991 (Box 19:, Folder 61)
    - Executive Committee Records, 1991 (Box 19:, Folder 62-63)
    - Board of Directors Records, 1992 (Box 19:, Folder 64)
    - Executive Committee Records, 1992 (Box 19:, Folder 65-66)
    - Board of Directors Records, 1993 (Box 19:, Folder 67-68)
    - Executive Committee Records, 1993 (Box 19:, Folder 69-70)
    - Board of Directors Records, 1994 (Box 19:, Folder 71-72)
    - Executive Committee Records, 1994 (Box 19:, Folder 73-74)
    - Board of Directors Records, 1995 (Box 20:, Folder 75-76)
    - Executive Committee Records, 1995 (Box 20:, Folder 77-78)
    - Board of Directors Records, 1996 (Box 20:, Folder 79-80)
    - Executive Committee Records, 1996 (Box 20:, Folder 81-84)
    - Board of Director Records, 1997 (Box 20:, Folder 85-86)
    - Executive Committee Records, 1997 (Box 20:, Folder 87-89)
    - Executive Committee Records, 1949-1951 (Box 20:, Folder 90)
    - Executive Committee Records, 1953-1954 (Box 20:, Folder 91)
    - Executive Committee Records, 1954-1956 (Box 20:, Folder 92)
    - Executive Committee Records, 1957-1959 (Box 20:, Folder 93)
    - Executive Committee Records, 1960 (Box 20:, Folder 94)
    - Executive Committee Records, 1961 (Box 20:, Folder 95)
    - Executive Committee Records, 1962 (Box 20:, Folder 96)
    - Executive Committee Records, 1963 (Box 21:, Folder 97)
    - Executive Committee Records, 1964 (Box 21:, Folder 98)
    - Executive Committee Records, 1965 (Box 21:, Folder 99)
    - Executive Committee Records, 1966 (Box 21:, Folder 100)
    - Executive Committee Records, 1967 (Box 21:, Folder 101)
    - Executive Committee Records, 1968 (Box 21:, Folder 102-103)
    - Executive Committee Records, 1969 (Box 21:, Folder 104-105)
    - Executive Committee Records, 1970 (Box 21:, Folder 106-107)
    - Executive Committee Records, 1971 (Box 21:, Folder 108-109)
    - Executive Committee Records, 1972 (Box 21:, Folder 110-111)
    - Executive Committee Records, 1973 (Box 21:, Folder 112-113)
    - Executive Committee Records, 1974 (Box 21:, Folder 114-115)
    - Executive Committee Records, 1975 (Box 21:, Folder 116-117)
    - Executive Committee Records, 1976 (Box 21:, Folder 118-119)
    - Executive Committee Records, 1977 (Box 21:, Folder 120-121)
    - Executive Committee Records, 1978 (Box 21:, Folder 122-123)
    - Executive Committee Records, 1979 (Box 22:, Folder 124-125)
    - Executive Committee Records, 1980 (Box 22:, Folder 126-127)
    - Executive Committee Records, 1981 (Box 22:, Folder 128-129)
  - Subseries C: Committee Records, 1955-1995
    - Audit Committee
      - 1955-1969 (Box 23:, Folder 130)
      - 1970 (Box 23:, Folder 131)
      - 1971 (Box 23:, Folder 132)
      - 1972 (Box 23:, Folder 133)
      - 1973 (Box 23:, Folder 134)
      - 1974 (Box 23:, Folder 135)
      - 1975 (Box 23:, Folder 136)
      - 1976 (Box 23:, Folder 137)
      - 1977 (Box 23:, Folder 138)
      - 1978 (Box 23:, Folder 139)
      - 1979 (Box 23:, Folder 140)
      - 1980 (Box 23:, Folder 141)
      - 1981 (Box 23:, Folder 142)
      - 1982 (Box 23:, Folder 143-144)
      - 1983 (Box 23:, Folder 145)
      - 1984 (Box 23:, Folder 146)
      - 1985 (Box 23:, Folder 147)
      - 1986 (Box 23:, Folder 148)
      - 1987 (Box 23:, Folder 149)
      - 1988 (Box 23:, Folder 150)
      - 1989 (Box 24:, Folder 151-152)
      - 1990 (Box 24:, Folder 153-154)
      - 1991 (Box 24:, Folder 155)
      - 1992 (Box 24:, Folder 156-157)
      - 1993 (Box 24:, Folder 158-160)
      - 1994 (Box 24:, Folder 161-162)
    - Bank Services & Operations Committee
      - 1970-1982 (Box 24:, Folder 163)
      - 1983-1985 (Box 24:, Folder 164)
      - 1986-1989 (Box 24:, Folder 165)
    - Commercial Loan Committee, 1983 (Box 24:, Folder 166)
    - Commercial Loan Department
      - Meeting Records, 1988-1990 (Box 24:, Folder 167)
      - Meeting Records, 1991-1992 (Box 24:, Folder 168)
      - Meeting Records, 1993 (Box 24:, Folder 169)
    - Committee Chairmen & Executive Committee Meeting Records, 1989 (Box 25:, Folder 170)
    - Community Involvement Committee Records, 1979-1989 (Box 25:, Folder 171)
    - Electronic Data Processing Steering Committee Records, 1984-1985 (Box 25:, Folder 172)
    - Joint Advisory Boards Meeting Records, 1966-1987 (Box 25:, Folder 173)
    - Joint Advisory Boards Meeting Records, 1988-1995 (Box 25:, Folder 174)
    - Long-Range Planning Committee Records, 1978-1980 (Box 25:, Folder 175)
    - Long-Range Planning Committee Records, 1981-1988 (Box 25:, Folder 176)
    - Name-Change Committees Records, 1976, 1980-1981 (Box 25:, Folder 177)
    - Name-Change Committee Records, 1989 (Box 25:, Folder 178)
    - Nominating Committee
      - 1973 (Box 25:, Folder 179)
      - 1975 (Box 25:, Folder 180)
      - 1976 (Box 25:, Folder 181)
      - 1977 (Box 25:, Folder 182)
      - 1978 (Box 25:, Folder 183)
      - 1979 (Box 25:, Folder 184)
      - 1980 (Box 25:, Folder 185)
      - 1981 (Box 25:, Folder 186)
      - 1982 (Box 25:, Folder 187)
      - 1983 (Box 25:, Folder 188)
      - 1984 (Box 25:, Folder 189)
      - 1985 (Box 25:, Folder 190)
      - 1987 (Box 25:, Folder 191)
      - 1988 (Box 25:, Folder 192)
      - 1989 (Box 25:, Folder 193)
      - 1990 (Box 25:, Folder 194)
      - 1991 (Box 25:, Folder 195)
      - 1992 (Box 25:, Folder 196)
      - 1993 (Box 25:, Folder 197)
      - 1994 (Box 25:, Folder 198)
    - Pension and Retirement Committee
      - 1959-1971 (Box 26:, Folder 199)
      - 1972-1974 (Box 26:, Folder 200)
      - 1975-1977 (Box 26:, Folder 201)
      - 1978-1982 (Box 26:, Folder 202)
      - 1983 (Box 26:, Folder 203-204)
      - 1984 (Box 26:, Folder 205)
      - 1985 (Box 26:, Folder 206)
      - 1986 (Box 26:, Folder 207)
      - 1987 (Box 26:, Folder 208)
      - 1988 (Box 26:, Folder 209)
      - 1989 (Box 26:, Folder 210)
      - 1990 (Box 26:, Folder 211-212)
    - Public Relations Committee
      - 1969-1972 (Box 27:, Folder 213)
      - 1973-1975 (Box 27:, Folder 214)
      - 1976-1979 (Box 27:, Folder 215)
      - 1980-1988 (Box 27:, Folder 216)
    - Search Committee Minutes, 1981-1983 (Box 27:, Folder 217)
    - Thrift Incentive Plan Committee Records, 1973-1975 (Box 27:, Folder 218)
    - "200 Million" Committee Records, 1976 (Box 27:, Folder 219)
  - Subseries D: Government Documents/Legal Records, 1941-1995
    - Call Reports - Condition & Income
      - 1985-1987 (Box 27:, Folder 220)
      - 1988 (Box 27:, Folder 221)
      - 1989 (Box 27:, Folder 222)
      - 1990 (Box 27:, Folder 223)
      - 1991 (Box 27:, Folder 224)
      - 1992 (Box 27:, Folder 225)
      - 1993 (Box 27:, Folder 226)
      - 1994 (Box 27:, Folder 227)
      - 1995 (Box 27:, Folder 228)
    - Certification - U.S. Savings Bonds, 1941-1945 (Box 27:, Folder 229)
    - Certification - F.D.I.C., 1969 (Box 27:, Folder 230)
    - Examinations
      - State of CT/F.D.I.C., 1969 (Box 27:, Folder 231)
      - State of CT/F.D.I.C., 1970 (Box 27:, Folder 232)
      - State of CT/F.D.I.C., 1971 (Box 27:, Folder 233)
      - State of CT/F.D.I.C., 1972 (Box 28:, Folder 234)
      - State of CT/F.D.I.C., 1973 (Box 28:, Folder 235)
      - F.D.I.C., 1974 (Box 28:, Folder 236)
      - State of CT, 1974 (Box 28:, Folder 237)
      - Truth-in-Lending - State of CT, 1974 (Box 28:, Folder 238)
      - F.D.I.C., 1975 (Box 28:, Folder 239)
      - State of CT, 1975 (Box 28:, Folder 240)
      - Joint State of CT/F.D.I.C., 1976 (Box 28:, Folder 241)
      - Joint State of CT/F.D.I.C./CT Truth-in-Lending, 1977 (Box 28:, Folder 242)
      - Joint State of CT/F.D.I.C./CT Truth-in-Lending, 1978 (Box 28:, Folder 243)
      - F.D.I.C. Compliance Reports, 1978 (Box 28:, Folder 244)
      - Joint State of CT/F.D.I.C./CT Truth-in-Lending, 1979 (Box 28:, Folder 245)
      - F.D.I.C., 1980 January (Box 28:, Folder 246)
      - Compliance Report F.D.I.C., 1980 July (Box 28:, Folder 247)
      - State of CT, 1981 (Box 28:, Folder 248)
      - Compliance Report on Fair Housing - F.D.I.C., 1981 (Box 28:, Folder 249)
      - State of CT, 1982 (Box 28:, Folder 250)
      - State of CT - Truth-in-Lending, 1982 (Box 28:, Folder 251)
      - Compliance Report - F.D.I.C., 1982 (Box 28:, Folder 252)
      - Truth-in-Lending Exam - State of CT, 1984 (Box 28:, Folder 253)
      - Electronic Data Processing Exam, & Compliance Reports - F.D.I.C., 1984 (Box 28:, Folder 254)
      - State of CT, 1985 (Box 28:, Folder 255)
      - Truth-in-Lending - State of CT, 1986 (Box 28:, Folder 256)
    - Legal Correspondence - Regarding SBM Charitable Foundation, 2004 (Box 28:, Folder 257)
    - Trademark Registration Records - Pfd., BottomLine, Conni, 1978-1983 (Box 28:, Folder 258)
  - Subseries E: Human Resources Materials, undated, 1973-2003
    - Bank President Resumes - Douglas Anderson, Richard Meduski, ca. 2003 (Box 29:, Folder 259)
    - Employee Handbook- "You and the S.B.M.", 2001 (Box 29:, Folder 260)
    - Employee Group Photo (B&W copy), 1973 (Box 29:, Folder 261)
    - Employee Retirement Plan Booklet, 1997 (Box 29:, Folder 262)
    - Employee Savings Plan Booklet, 2003 (Box 29:, Folder 263)
    - Employee Stock Ownership Plan, 2000 (Box 29:, Folder 264)
    - Job Descriptions
      - Accounting, 2001-2003 (Box 29:, Folder 265)
      - Answering Center, 2001-2002 (Box 29:, Folder 266)
      - Area Lending, 2002-2003 (Box 29:, Folder 267)
      - Audit, 2000-2003 (Box 29:, Folder 268)
      - Branch Administration, 2000-2003 (Box 29:, Folder 269)
      - Collections, 2001-2003 (Box 29:, Folder 270)
      - Commercial Loans, 2001-2003 (Box 29:, Folder 271)
      - Commercial Mortgage, 2002-2003 (Box 29:, Folder 272)
      - Executive, 2001-2003 (Box 29:, Folder 273)
      - Facilities, 2003 (Box 29:, Folder 274)
      - Finance, 2000-2003 (Box 29:, Folder 275)
      - General Services, 2001-2002 (Box 29:, Folder 276)
      - Human Resources, 1999-2003 (Box 29:, Folder 277)
      - Infinex/SBLI, 2001-2002 (Box 29:, Folder 278)
      - Information Systems, 2002-2003 (Box 29:, Folder 279)
      - Loan Administration, 2001-2003 (Box 29:, Folder 280)
      - Loan/Deposit Servicing, Commercial, 1998-2003 (Box 29:, Folder 281)
      - Loan/Deposit Servicing, Consumer, 1998-2003 (Box 29:, Folder 282)
      - Loan/Deposit Servicing, Deposit Services, 1998-2003 (Box 29:, Folder 283)
      - Marketing, 1998-2002 (Box 29:, Folder 284)
      - Merchant Service Center, Sturbridge, 2002-2003 (Box 29:, Folder 285)
      - Merchant Service, 2000-2003 (Box 29:, Folder 286)
      - Origination, 2002 (Box 29:, Folder 287)
      - Outside Origination, 1998-2003 (Box 29:, Folder 288)
      - Processing, 2000-2003 (Box 30:, Folder 289)
      - Proof Reconcilliation, 1998-2002 (Box 30:, Folder 290)
      - Residential Construction, 2000-2003 (Box 30:, Folder 291)
      - Security, 2001-2003 (Box 30:, Folder 292)
      - Training Center, 2002 (Box 30:, Folder 293)
    - Supervisory Handbook, 2002 (Box 30:, Folder 294-295)
    - Tee Shirt Distribution Records, 1991 (Box 30:, Folder 296)
    - Training Workbook-Microsoft Outlook 98, ca.1998 (Box 30:, Folder 297)
- Series II: Financial Records, undated, 1905-1995
  - Subseries A: Ledgers, 1905-1955
    - Accounts Journal, 1905-1913 (Box 31)
    - General Ledger, 1905-1915 (Box 32)
    - General Ledger, 1915-1953 (Box 33)
    - General Ledger, ca. 1953-1955 (Box 34)
  - Subseries B: Statements of Financial Condition, 1955-1995
    - Directors Reports
      - 1958 (Box 28:, Folder 298)
      - 1959-1960 (Box 28:, Folder 299)
      - 1962 (Box 28:, Folder 300)
      - 1963 (Box 28:, Folder 301)
    - Permanent Record of Loan Approvals
      - 1955 (Box 28:, Folder 302)
      - 1956 (Box 28:, Folder 303)
      - 1957 (Box 28:, Folder 304)
      - 1958 (Box 28:, Folder 305)
      - 1959 (Box 28:, Folder 306)
      - 1960 (Box 28:, Folder 307)
      - 1961 (Box 28:, Folder 308)
      - 1962 (Box 35:, Folder 309)
      - 1963 (Box 35:, Folder 310)
      - 1964 (Box 35:, Folder 311-312)
      - 1965 (Box 35:, Folder 313-314)
      - 1966 (Box 35:, Folder 315-317)
      - 1967 (Box 35:, Folder 318-321)
      - 1968 (Box 35:, Folder 322-325)
      - 1969 (Box 35:, Folder 326-329)
      - 1970 (Box 36:, Folder 330-333)
    - Statements of Condition
      - 1971 (Box 36:, Folder 334-336)
      - 1972 (Box 36:, Folder 337-338)
      - 1973 (Box 36:, Folder 339-340)
      - 1974 (Box 36:, Folder 341-342)
      - 1975 (Box 36:, Folder 343-344)
      - 1976 (Box 36:, Folder 345-348)
      - 1977 (Box 37:, Folder 349-352)
      - 1978 (Box 37:, Folder 353-356)
      - 1979 (Box 37:, Folder 357-359)
      - 1980 (Box 37:, Folder 360-361)
      - 1981 (Box 37:, Folder 362-363)
      - 1982 (Box 37:, Folder 364-365)
      - 1983 (Box 37:, Folder 366-367)
      - 1984 (Box 38:, Folder 368-369)
      - 1985 (Box 38:, Folder 370-371)
      - 1986 (Box 38:, Folder 372-373)
      - 1987 (Box 38:, Folder 374-375)
      - 1988 (Box 38:, Folder 376-377)
      - 1989 (Box 38:, Folder 378-379)
      - 1990 (Box 38:, Folder 380-381)
      - 1991 (Box 38:, Folder 382-383)
      - 1992 (Box 39:, Folder 384-385)
      - 1993 (Box 39:, Folder 386-387)
      - 1994 (Box 39:, Folder 388-389)
      - 1995 (Box 39:, Folder 390-391)
  - Subseries C: Stock Records - Home Bank & Trust Company, 1920-1934
    - Shareholders Ledger, 1920-1934 (Box 69)
    - Stock Certificate Book, 1920-1929 (Box 70)
- Series III: Advertising and Public Relations Records, undated, 1839, 1905-2004
  - Subseries A: Advertising Records, 1982-2000
    - Ad Schedule for News Media, 1982 (Box 39:, Folder 392)
    - Ad Schedule for News Media, 1983,1986 (Box 39:, Folder 393)
    - Commercial Survey Information, 1990 (Box 39:, Folder 394)
    - Loan Rate Sheets, 1990 (Box 39:, Folder 395)
    - Loan Rate Sheets, 1991 (Box 39:, Folder 396)
    - Budget, Surveys, Memos, other documents, 1991 (Box 39:, Folder 397)
    - Loan Rate Sheets, 1992 (Box 39:, Folder 398)
    - Marketing Budget Information, 1992 (Box 39:, Folder 399)
    - Advertising Records, 1993 (Box 39:, Folder 400)
    - Loan Rate Sheets, 1993 (Box 39:, Folder 401)
    - Advertisement Planning Records, 1994 (Box 39:, Folder 402-403)
    - Advertising Policy, 1994 (Box 39:, Folder 404)
    - Expenditures; Misc., 1994 (Box 39:, Folder 405)
    - Financial Statement (MISER), 1994 (Box 39:, Folder 406)
    - Marketing Budgets and Invoices, 1994 (Box 39:, Folder 407)
    - Media Ad Records, 1994 (Box 39:, Folder 408-409)
    - Account Book, 1995 (Box 40:, Folder 410-411)
    - Advertising Records, 1995 (Box 40:, Folder 412-413)
    - Media Plan and Budget, 1995 (Box 40:, Folder 414)
    - Plan Recommendation, 1995 (Box 40:, Folder 415)
    - Rate Ads and Schedules, 1995 (Box 40:, Folder 416)
    - Account Book, 1996 (Box 40:, Folder 417-418)
    - Expenditures, 1996 (Box 40:, Folder 419)
    - Marketing Research Report- "West of the River Markets", 1996 (Box 40:, Folder 420)
    - Weekly Ads and Rates, 1996 (Box 40:, Folder 421)
    - Rate Ad Schedules, 1997 (Box 40:, Folder 422)
    - Marketing Plan, 1998 (Box 40:, Folder 423)
    - Magazine Ranking of CT Banks, By Assets, 1998 (Box 40:, Folder 424)
    - Advertising Policy, 2000 (Box 40:, Folder 425)
  - Subseries B: Brochures, 1945-2001
    - Assorted S.B.M. Brochures, ca. 1960s-ca.2000 (Box 40:, Folder 426)
    - "Connecticut Bancshares, Inc." (draft), 2000 (Box 40:, Folder 427)
    - On-line Banking, 1998 (Box 40:, Folder 428)
    - Statement of Condition
      - 1945-1960 (Box 40:, Folder 429)
      - 1961-1972 (Box 40:, Folder 430)
      - 1973-1979 (Box 40:, Folder 431)
      - 1980-1986 (Box 40:, Folder 432)
      - 1987-1991 (Box 40:, Folder 433)
      - 1992-1997 (Box 41:, Folder 434)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 41:, Folder 435)
    - "Welcome" Brochures, undated, 1996, 2001 (Box 41:, Folder 436)
  - Subseries C: Newsletters, ca. 1980-1994
    - Employee Newsletter - Names Submitted by Employees, 1991 (Box 41:, Folder 437)
    - Employee Newsletters and Source Material
      - 1991 (Box 41:, Folder 438)
      - 1992 (Box 41:, Folder 439-440)
      - 1993 (Box 41:, Folder 441-442)
      - 1994 (Box 41:, Folder 443)
    - Outside Newsletter Samples, 1980s (Box 41:, Folder 444-445)
  - Subseries D: Advertisements, 1923-2004
    - Advertisement Drafts/Drawings (4), undated, ca.1990s (Box 62)
    - Advertisement Scrapbooks
      - 1968-1970 (Box 42)
      - 1970-1972 (Box 43)
      - 1972-1974 (Box 44)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 45)
      - 1976-1978 (Box 46)
      - 1978-1981 (Box 47)
      - 1982-1983 (Box 48)
    - Advertisements - Newspaper
      - 1995 (Box 41:, Folder 446-449)
      - 1996 (Box 41:, Folder 450-452)
      - 1997 (Box 41:, Folder 453-455)
      - 1999 (Box 41:, Folder 456)
      - 2000 (Box 41:, Folder 457)
      - 2001 (Box 41:, Folder 458)